Guide to the Stanford University, Chicano Fellows Program, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Chicano Fellows Program, records
1970s-1980s
SC0547
Stanford University. Chicano Fellows Program
43 Linear feet
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
The materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Access Terms
Stanford University. Chicano Fellows Program
Collection Contents
- Records, Accession ARCH-1983-034
  - Brochures for Stanford Chicano/a students, Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Minutes from General Assembly and miscellaneous notes, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Chicanas and minority women, assorted reports (photocopies, Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Chicanas and minority women, assorted reports (photocopies), Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Chicano perceptions of high School and Chicano performance, report (photocopy) by Ruben W. Espinosa, Celestino Fernandez, and Sanford M. Dornbusch, Stanford University, Circa 1976 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Ethnic minority theme houses at Stanford: minutes, reports, etc. of the subcommittee on minority affairs, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Final report of special study committee number two on student employment, Stanford University, 1970 May 30 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Final report to the NEH Mexican-American seminar, Stanford University, project director John J. Johnson, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Hvolboll, Eric, “The property God has given me: a brief and unfinished story of the Ortega family and their Rancho Nuestra Senora del Refugio, Santa Barbara County,” history honors thesis, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Congressional papers, 1969-1975 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 7th International bilingual bicultural education conference, Puerto Rico, papers and publications, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Minorities and medicine in the United States, a collection of article summaries and complete articles for an amicus curias brief for the national lawyers Guild in Bakke v. Regents, compiled by Eric S. Goldman, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Preferential law school admissions and the equal protection clause: an analysis of the competing arguments, prepared for the Law School Admission Council [University of Washington] by Martin M. Redish, Circa 1976 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Chicano reference library – subject terms and various forms, Undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Chicano reference library, books ordered and out of print, 1976-1981 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Chicano library – memoranda, bibliography, and miscellaneous records, Undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Chicano library Manua, Undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Photograph album subjects include Semana de la Raza 1969, Renato Rosaldo, Teatro Urbano, Chicano Moratorium in Los Angeles 1970, social events, and individual students., 1969-1973 and undated (Box 3 os)
- Records, Accession ARCH-1996-017
- Records, Accession ARCH-1997-143